Pattern,issue1,output1
PS_ONLY,"Question: """""" I noticed my old word2vec files stopped working, so I made some new ones,  using the writeFullModel function. But it seems the only thing it stores are the vectors, not the words? and loadFullModel also can't load the file the fitted model in the memory works fine, it seems saving it is where the problem is. Should I use writeFullModel, or should I save it in a different way? """"""
Answer: ","The sentence """""" But it seems the only thing it stores are the vectors, not the words? """""" uses <pattern>the only thing it VBZ</pattern> to describe the limitation of ""writeFullModel function"".  The answer is YES."
PS_PROBLEM,"Question: """""" Im having trouble trying to update some data using and api called ""crud:crud"", I can ""get"" and ""post"" fine but ""put"" is giving me this error. How could I fix that? """"""
Answer: ","The sentence """""" Im having trouble trying to update some data using and api called ""crud:crud"" """""" uses <pattern>having trouble VBG</pattern> to indicate that there is something wrong when ""trying to update some data"". The answer is YES."
PS_NEG_VERB,"Question: """""" Hey guys, any ideas on why a test executes perfectly on a real android device, but .waitForElementById and .elementById will fail every time when I run the same exact test on SauceLabs (Android Emulator)? I'm using node bindings and the latest versions of everything. ""Error response status: 7, , NoSuchElement - An element could not be located on the page using the given search parameters"" """"""
Answer: ","The sentence """""" but .waitForElementById and .elementById will fail every time when I run the same exact test on SauceLabs (Android Emulator)? """""" uses <pattern>sth will fail every time</pattern> to indicate that there is something wrong with "".waitForElementById and .elementById"". The answer is YES."
PS_PROBLEM_IS,"Question: """""" Anyone knows a good solution to use php-cli and keep the container running it alive? I'm trying to run a micro service (Lumen) by only using php-cli. But the problem is that my container exits by itself Probably because php-cli is not running a daemon """"""
Answer: ","The sentence """""" But the problem is that my container exits by itself Probably because php-cli is not running a daemon """""" uses <pattern>the problem is that</pattern> to indicate that ""container exits by itself"" is an undesired behavior. The answer is YES."
PS_NEG_AUX_ADV_ADJ,"Question: """""" roychri: , can you help me out with sessions. How can I add a variable into session variable which will be available during whole session. Seems like my session variable is getting refreshed when I access any link. Here is my app.js [<-LINK->] roychri: , it's here [<-LINK->] line 23 roychri: , the data variable that added, is not available in other routes. roychri: ok. Let me have a look again Thanks """"""
Answer: ","The sentence """""" the data variable that added, is not available in other routes. """""" uses <pattern>not available in sth</pattern> to indicate that there is something wrong with ""data variable"". The answer is YES."
PS_SEEMS_TO_NEG_VERB,"Question: """""" I'm trying to type-guard on a discriminant property with Array.prototype.includes but that doesn't seem to work (2.8.1), didn't find anything searching through the issue tracker. Here is a gist of the principle [<-LINK->] """"""
Answer: ","The sentence """""" I'm trying to type-guard on a discriminant property with Array.prototype.includes but that doesn't seem to work (2.8.1) """""" uses <pattern>doesn't seem to VB</pattern> to indicate that there is something wrong when ""trying to type-guard"". The answer is YES."
PS_NEG_ADV_ADJ,"Question: """""" Anyone good with git? I'm getting some weird behavior and I can't quite make sense of it. when I do git rebase -i HEAD~3, it shows the commits in this order:  ``` commit 1 commit 2 commit 3 ```. I would expect it to be: ``` commit 3 commit 2 commit 1 ``` """"""
Answer: ","The sentence """""" I'm getting some weird behavior and I can't quite make sense of it. """""" uses an undesired adjective <pattern>weird</pattern> to indicate that the user is getting something wrong. The answer is YES."
PS_VERB_ERROR,"Question: """""" Hi, i new here and i'm workin in some app with angular when execute the application show me this error  ""You provided an invalid object where a stream was expected"". You can provide an Observable, Promise, Array, or Iterable. any ideas ? """"""
Answer: ","The sentence """""" i new here and i'm workin in some app with angular when execute the application show me this error """""" uses <pattern>VB PRP this error</pattern> to show the error which the user is currently encountering. The answer is YES."
PS_NEG_AUX_VERB,"Question: """""" The ethereum wallet isn't finishing downloading.. Does anyone have this problem also? Stuck at Downloading block 892,148 of 4,637,826,Downloading chain structure 3,297,848 of 3,325,840 Any advice? Maybe I do need to put my laptop under the crane? XD Okay the running water was the fix. THANKS! """"""
Answer: ","The sentence """""" The ethereum wallet isn't finishing downloading. """""" uses <pattern>sth isn't finishing VBG</pattern> to indicate that there is something wrong with ""ethereum wallet"". The answer is YES."
PS_VERB_NO,"Question: """""" any ideas on how i may be able to find the circular dependency? i tried adding the `--verbose` flag to the ng build command but that didn't really help tried using this tool [link], but it reports no circular dependencies. i've also looked through the code and nothing really stands out """"""
Answer: ","The sentence """""" tried using this tool [link], but it reports no circular dependencies """""" uses <pattern>reports no JJ NNS</pattern> to indicate that there is something wrong with ""this tool"". The answer is YES."
PS_ONLY,"Question: """""" hi, I'm using a CNN similar to this given in the CnnSentenceClassificationExample. The following exception occurs: UnsupportedOperationException: Masked global pooling with on CNN data currently only supports data with h=1 or w=1. Anyone encountered this before? """"""
Answer: ","The sentence """""" Masked global pooling with on CNN data currently only supports data with h=1 or w=1. """""" uses <pattern>sth currently only supports sth</pattern> to describe the limitation of the method which the user is currently trying. The answer is YES."
PS_PROBLEM,"Question: """""" Hi! I am seeing some issues with DataVec and the stringToTimeTransform behaviour.  For example,  I tried to output the milliseconds timestamps as produced by the transform on the Basic DataVec Example data (I modified the csv to have entries where month is not only January(i.e. 01). """"""
Answer: ","The sentence """""" I am seeing some issues with DataVec and the stringToTimeTransform behaviour. """""" uses <pattern>seeing some issues with sth</pattern> to describe the problem which the user is currently encountering. The answer is YES."
PS_NEG_VERB,"Question: """""" has anyone had success with dockerized jenkins running docker within? I've volume moutned docker, and from within the container i am able to fully do anything i want with docker, but jenkins is complaining access denied (i'm testing with jenkins user of course).... this was working earlier today just fine, i just restarted all the services due to a non-related service change. now all of a sudden it's access denied non-stop from the jenkins ui (again, inside the container works fine) """"""
Answer: ","The sentence """""" but jenkins is complaining access denied """""" uses <pattern>sth is complaining [anomaly]</pattern> to describe the problem which the user is currently encountering. The answer is YES."
PS_PROBLEM_IS,"Question: """""" Hi, I am training a word2vec model on a preprocessed wiki corpus using popular frameworks like tensorflow, gensim, originalc and dl4j. The issue is that dl4j's vocab size doesn't seem to be matching other framework's vocab size (456,940words for all other frameworks while it is454,022for dl4j formin_count=30). These vocab sizes are consistent across multiple runs on various cloud instances. What could be causing this? Weirdly, dl4j's vocab size matches other frameworks when trained on wiki corpus.Link to [<-LINK->] . """"""
Answer:","The sentence """""" The issue is that dl4j's vocab size doesn't seem to be matching other framework's vocab size """""" uses <pattern>the issue is that</pattern> to describe the problem which the user is currently encountering. The answer is YES."
PS_NEG_AUX_ADV_ADJ,"Question: """""" Hello guys, How can I represent a type, that is not assignable to another type? Like T extends U, but in reverse way I know there is no ""T not extends U"" so how can I do that And I can't use the false branch of the conditional types in my context """"""
Answer: ","The sentence """""" that is not assignable to another type """""" uses <pattern>not assignable to sth</pattern> to describe the problem which the user is currently encountering. The answer is YES."
PS_SEEMS_TO_NEG_VERB,"Question: """""" can someone help me with a higher order component? I can't seem to pass my props down. It seems like setState property is missing thanks! [<-CODE->] and then I would use it with a Dashboard component [<-CODE->] I added some <any>s cause I was unsure of myself, but it was more strongly typed before I went down the rabbit hole Additionally, I had tried [<-CODE->] """"""
Answer: ","The sentence """""" I can't seem to pass my props down. """""" uses <pattern>can't seem to VB</pattern> to describe the problem which the user is currently encountering. The answer is YES."
PS_NEG_ADV_ADJ,"Question: """""" I am unable to align column using jspdf. Will you please guide what should I modify in this code?  """"""
Answer: ","The sentence """""" I am unable to align column using jspdf. """""" uses <pattern>be unable to VB</pattern> to indicate that the user is getting something wrong. The answer is YES."
PS_VERB_ERROR,"Question: """""" hey guys sorry for raising question here but if somebody can help me out. I am trying to read a json file and checking whether a key is present or not if key present the its value will be returned.  But i am getting error ""cannot read property 'data' of undefined . my json file """"""
Answer: ","The sentence """""" But i am getting error """""" uses <pattern>VBG error</pattern> to show the error which the user is currently encountering. The answer is YES."
PS_NEG_AUX_VERB,"Question: """""" Hi, I think there might be a problem in MovingWindowDataSetFetcher. It calls MovingWindowMatrix.windows with flattened and addRotate both set to true. However, I think this causes a problem since a flattened matrix can't be rotated because it fails the isMatrix test. Am i mistaken? """"""
Answer: ","The sentence """""" I think this causes a problem since a flattened matrix can't be rotated because it fails the isMatrix test. """""" uses <pattern>sth can't be VBN</pattern> to describe the problem which the user is currently encountering. The answer is YES."
PS_VERB_NO,"Question: """""" Hey, just wondering who I should contact for problems with BTC to ETH transactions in my Ethereum wallet? Basically, I ordered 0.1 Ethereum via Bitcoin in my Ethereum wallet (0.8.9) yesterday. Although the bitcoin transaction was confirmed several hours ago (and currently stands with 36 confirmations), I'm still seeing 0 Ethers in my account. Crab29: Hey, do you have any idea what's happening? """"""
Answer: ","The sentence """"""  I'm still seeing 0 Ethers in my account. """""" uses <pattern>seeing 0 NNS</pattern> to describe the problem which the user is currently encountering. The answer is YES."
PS_ONLY,"Question: """""" is it possible to get client private ip in angular, please help. i tried this [link], but it is returning only the public ip. any other way to private ip example :192.168.56.X. """"""
Answer: ","The sentence """""" but it is returning only the public ip. """""" uses <pattern>it is VBG only sth</pattern> to describe the limitation of the method which the user is currently trying. The answer is YES."
PS_PROBLEM,"Question: """""" Trying to come up with a generic pattern validation directive since none is built in, but running into an issue of only getting the string name of the variable passed to the directive instead of the variable itself... any ideas? """"""
Answer:","The sentence """""" but running into an issue of only getting the string name of the variable passed to the directive instead of the variable itself """""" uses <pattern>running into an issue of VBG</pattern> to describe the problem which the user is currently encountering. The answer is YES."
PS_NEG_VERB,"Question: """""" Hi. I have a container element with overflow: auto. On a mobile device, I can only scroll when I touch an area in the container that is not filled by a child component. It seems like the child components are blocking the touch scroll event. How can I fix this? """"""
Answer: ","The sentence """""" It seems like the child components are blocking the touch scroll event. """""" uses <pattern>sth are blocking sth</pattern> to describe the problem which the user is currently encountering. The answer is YES."
PS_PROBLEM_IS,"Question: """""" hey guys i've got a form in a modal popup, and i wan make a post request to my server the request goes successfully with a 200 status response but my issue is that my data doesn't get sent to the server above is my code snippet. can anyone help-out """"""
Answer:","The sentence """""" but my issue is that my data doesn't get sent to the server above is my code snippet """""" uses <pattern>my issue is that</pattern> to describe the problem which the user is currently encountering. The answer is YES."
PS_NEG_AUX_ADV_ADJ,"Question: """""" Hi All,  i have a trained LSTM serving in production. while doing prediction continously using ""model.output(input)"" suddenly massive amounts of threads are getting created ending up in restarting the server. I am not able to trace the reason. Please enlight me on this Thread counts are suddenly spiking from 100's to 1000's for very few seconds """"""
Answer: ","The sentence """""" I am not able to trace the reason. """""" uses <pattern>not able to VB</pattern> to describe the problem which the user is currently encountering. The answer is YES."
PS_SEEMS_TO_NEG_VERB,"Question: """""" I'm in the middle of figuring out my own macro system lol  [<-LINK->]. it works so well for expanding macros and giving me info about each expansion. But my brain can't seem to process how to use the info to trace text ranges through the expansion. Recursion is probably fucking with my brain. There's one more layer of expansion I have to map out. I'm so immature  [<-LINK->] I giggled at that line of code  [<-LINK->] """"""
Answer: ","The sentence """""" But my brain can't seem to process how to use the info to trace text ranges through the expansion. """""" uses <pattern>can't seem to VB</pattern> to describe the problem which the user is currently encountering. The answer is YES."
PS_NEG_ADV_ADJ,"Question: """""" Could anyone help me explain why the following code seems correct, though to me it seems like it's not? [<-CODE->] returning a string here compiles and runs though I tell it that it should be a void method SalathielGenese: that's exactly my point, the code is wrong but it doesn't give me an error to me it seems like a bug  """"""
Answer: ","The sentence """""" the code is wrong but it doesn't give me an error to me it seems like a bug """""" uses an undesired adjective <pattern>wrong</pattern> to indicate that there is something wrong with the code. The answer is YES."
PS_VERB_ERROR,"Question: """""" I've downloaded the BLAS libraries and I've set the path according to: [<-LINK->]. but when I run the DL4j examples I got the warning that BLAS is not installed.  How can I activate BLAS ? if you train the network for a specific problem the DL4J will save the net parameters to work with them later ? """"""
Answer: ","The sentence """""" but when I run the DL4j examples I got the warning that BLAS is not installed. """""" uses <pattern>VBP the warning that</pattern> to show the error which the user is currently encountering. The answer is YES."
PS_NEG_AUX_VERB,"Question: """""" hello, i have a problem with named router-outlet, i need to add dialogs in a named router-outlet, but as i heard from github/angular, i can't use lazy loaded modules with auxiliary routes. Is there a way to do that now? """"""
Answer: ","The sentence """""" i can't use lazy loaded modules with auxiliary routes. """""" uses <pattern>i can't VB</pattern> to describe the problem which the user is currently encountering. The answer is YES."
PS_VERB_NO,"Question: """""" hey - can i get some n00b help. I have the following message ""[ts] Cannot invoke an expression whose type lacks a call signature. Type 'Action<any, any>' has no compatible call signatures."" but cant wrap my head around whats going on """"""
Answer: ","The sentence """"""  Type 'Action<any, any>' has no compatible call signatures """""" uses <pattern>has no JJ NN</pattern> to describe the problem which the user is currently encountering. The answer is YES."
PS_ONLY,"Question: """""" Does anyone know of a way to determine if a type could also refer to a value?  That is, if the type is of a Class, then do one conditional type branch, and if it is only an Interface or primitive then it will use the other branch. """"""
Answer: ","The sentence """""" and if it is only an Interface or primitive then it will use the other branch """""" uses <pattern>if it is only</pattern> to describe one condition of the example instead of describing the problem, so the answer is NO."
PS_PROBLEM,"Question: """""" Question about Observables: If I have Observable A, and things are subscribed to it, is there a way to take Observable B and merge it into A so that all of As subscriptions are notified of the elements in B? """"""
Answer: ","The sentence """""" Question about Observables: """""" uses <pattern>question about sth</pattern> but after the semi-colon, it is only an example to describe the user's expectation instead of describing the problem, so the answer is NO."
PS_NEG_VERB,"Question: """""" Are there performance gains to be had by breaking up a medium size component template into many smaller components w/ inputs for their relevant pieces of data? I understand the organizational benefits of having small, laser-focused components, I'm just on the fence about how granular I should be getting. """"""
Answer: ","The sentence """""" Are there performance gains to be had by breaking up a medium size component template into many smaller components w/ inputs for their relevant pieces of data? """""" uses an undesired verb phrase <pattern>breaking up sth</pattern> but ""breaking up a medium size component"" is the intention of the user, not the problem which the user is currently encountering, so the answer is NO."
PS_PROBLEM_IS,"Question: """""" Hi guys. How can I use Docker with Angular CLI? I want to be able to build my app and push it to a production docker container that is serving nginx as well. So the problem is, I want to build a dist folder in the docker container, and during development I would be able to watch the folder and serve the webapp. Anyone could provide some guidance on how I could do this? """"""
Answer: ","The sentence """""" So the problem is """""" uses <pattern>the problem is</pattern> but the following contents are the user's expectation instead of describing the problem, so the answer is NO."
PS_NEG_AUX_ADV_ADJ,"Question: """""" I'm buying bitcoin from someone via Localbitcoin, my aim is like@Swinks95, I want to leave the ether I get in for a while, maybe a  couple of years/months, not sure yet. I was going to change the bitcoin I buy to ether via shapeshift.io. do you know if that  site is reliable? I have solarpanels on my roof!! Haha maybe I'll wait till some point in the future if  it's not so rewarding """"""
Answer: ","The sentence """""" maybe a  couple of years/months, not sure yet """""" uses <pattern>not sure</pattern> but it has nothing to do with describing the problem which the user is currently encountering, so the answer is NO."
PS_SEEMS_TO_NEG_VERB,"Question: """""" I'm in the middle of figuring out my own macro system lol  [<-LINK->]. it works so well for expanding macros and giving me info about each expansion. But my brain can't seem to process how to use the info to trace text ranges through the expansion. Recursion is probably fucking with my brain. There's one more layer of expansion I have to map out. I'm so immature  [<-LINK->]. I giggled at that line of code  [<-LINK->] """"""
Answer: ","The sentence """""" But my brain can't seem to process how to use the info to trace text ranges through the expansion """""" uses <pattern>can't seem to VB</pattern> but this is the user's expectation instead of describing the problem, so the answer is NO."
PS_NEG_ADV_ADJ,"Question: """""" Any idea on how to provider a service to two different lazy loaded modules in the best way? It is funny in some places (stackeroverflow) guys are saying that having services in a shared module is bad practice and others say it is the right way :D """"""
Answer: ","The sentence """""" It is funny in some places (stackeroverflow) guys are saying that having services in a shared module is bad practice and others say it is the right way :D """""" uses <pattern>sth is bad practice</pattern> but it is said by some other guys, not represents the user's point, so the answer is NO."
PS_VERB_ERROR,"Question: """""" Hi everyone, does anyone know how to get the mat-error and mat-hit animations? I have made a custom the mat-error and mat-hint like elements and would like to animate them exactly as in material. Thank you. """"""
Answer: ","The sentence """"""  does anyone know how to get the mat-error and mat-hit animations? """""" uses <pattern>get the mat-error</pattern> but this pattern is in the ""how-to"" question, it is only the user's expectation instead of describing the problem, so the answer is NO."
PS_NEG_AUX_VERB,"Question: """""" Hi guys, what is the next step after [<-LINK->] ? deep net for classification, prediction, sentiment analysis, yes but how to ? Only available examples do it by using already separated positive/negative data. Can't we use google Word2Vec file (1.5Go) to do that ? """"""
Answer: ","The sentence """"""  Can't we use google Word2Vec file (1.5Go) to do that ? """""" uses <pattern>can't .. VB</pattern> but this is just a rhetorical question instead of describing the problem, so the answer is NO."
PS_VERB_NO,"Question: """""" Hi, is there any way to detect no router change? I mean situation when user click the same routerLink he is allready in i would like to implement some monkeyPatch for forcing angular 4 router to reinitialize route """"""
Answer: ","The sentence """"""  is there any way to detect no router change? """""" uses <pattern>detect no router change</pattern> but ""no router change"" is a noun phrase here to indicate the user's expectation instead of describing the problem, so the answer is NO."
